palmbeachstate.edu 2013-12-04

# Palm Beach State - Internet Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting Palm Beach State College’s Web site. Your privacy is very important to us. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you choose to make such information available to us. 

When you visit our Web site, our server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, we monitor the volume and timing of access to our site by collecting information on the date, time and pages accessed by visitors. We do this so that we can improve the content of our Web site, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and individual visitors’ personal information is not identified. 

If you choose to share personal information with us – by sending us a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information – we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the Information may be saved for a designated period to comply with Florida’s archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law. 

If you have any other questions about our privacy procedures, or have ideas about improving our procedures, please feel free to e-mail us at [webmaster@palmbeachstate.edu](mailto:webmaster@palmbeachstate.edu). Approved by President’s Staff on August 15, 2000.
